<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<PassiveXmlRoot xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <Passive ID="37770001">
    <Negative>false</Negative>
    <IsHide>false</IsHide>
    <Rarity>Unique</Rarity>
    <Lock>false</Lock>
    <CanGivePassive>false</CanGivePassive>
    <CanReceivePassive>false</CanReceivePassive>
    <InnerType>-1</InnerType>
    <Cost>777</Cost>
    <Script>CindGray_PlayerManager</Script>
    <Name>The Gray Cinderella / The Ashen Monster</Name>
    <Desc>At the start of each Wave, heal to 50% Max HP if below, and gain The Gray Cinderella passive. 
	
Once per Wave, upon taking lethal damage, negate it and gain damage immunity for the rest of the Scene instead. When this occurs, recover from Stagger and heal 50% of your Max HP, and change The Gray Cinderella status to The Ashen Monster at the start of the next Scene.
	
At Emotion Level 2+, add 'Triumphant Pulse' to the Personal E.G.O hand. While in The Ashen Monster form, also add 'Dawnlit Ashen Trail: Cinderella Gray' to your E.G.O hand.</Desc>
  </Passive>
  <Passive ID="37770002">
    <Negative>false</Negative>
    <IsHide>false</IsHide>
    <Rarity>Unique</Rarity>
    <Lock>false</Lock>
    <CanGivePassive>false</CanGivePassive>
    <CanReceivePassive>false</CanReceivePassive>
    <InnerType>-1</InnerType>
    <Cost>7</Cost>
    <Script>CindGray_StarlightOfKasamatsu</Script>
    <Name>Starlight of Kasamatsu</Name>
    <Desc>Gain 1 Haste next Scene. If this unit is in the upper half of the percentile of the faster units, gain 3 Haste instead. If the Speed difference between this unit and the target are greater than 3, the target loses Power equal to the Speed difference reduced by 2</Desc>
  </Passive>
  <Passive ID="37770003">
    <Negative>false</Negative>
    <IsHide>false</IsHide>
    <Rarity>Unique</Rarity>
    <Lock>false</Lock>
    <CanGivePassive>false</CanGivePassive>
    <CanReceivePassive>false</CanReceivePassive>
    <InnerType>-1</InnerType>
    <Cost>7</Cost>
    <Script>CindGray_Monster</Script>
    <Name>Monster</Name>
    <Desc>At the end of the Scene, take 1% max HP damage. This increases by 1.5% per Scene (max of 12% total, additive). Gain Craving Monster / Hungry Monster / Starved Monster based on remaining HP on self. At the start of the Scene, if a non-allied unit Staggered the previous Turn, healing effects are x1.46 more effective, x1.738 if they were defeated instead. Additionally, attacking Staggered enemies restores HP based on the Monster status effect</Desc>
  </Passive>
    <Passive ID="37770004">
    <Negative>false</Negative>
    <IsHide>false</IsHide>
    <Rarity>Unique</Rarity>
    <Lock>false</Lock>
    <CanGivePassive>false</CanGivePassive>
    <CanReceivePassive>false</CanReceivePassive>
    <InnerType>-1</InnerType>
    <Cost>7</Cost>
    <Script>CindGray_UndyingFlame</Script>
    <Name>Undying Flame</Name>
    <Desc>Upon taking lethal damage, and all other death prevention effects have been expended, become briefly immune to all forms of damage and gain a surge of strength. When triggered, recover from Stagger next turn, become immune to damage and stagger damage for the next turn, recover all Light, draw 5 pages, become unable to be healed, and gain +2 Min and Max Power. On the end of that particular Scene, die.</Desc>
  </Passive>
   <Passive ID="37770005">
    <Negative>false</Negative>
    <IsHide>true</IsHide>
    <Rarity>Unique</Rarity>
    <Lock>false</Lock>
    <CanGivePassive>false</CanGivePassive>
    <CanReceivePassive>false</CanReceivePassive>
    <InnerType>-1</InnerType>
    <Cost>7</Cost>
    <Script>CindGray_BossDiceAdd</Script>
    <Name>Speed - Triple 7s</Name>
    <Desc>Gain +3 Speed dice.</Desc>
  </Passive>
  <Passive ID="37770006">
    <Negative>false</Negative>
    <IsHide>false</IsHide>
    <Rarity>Unique</Rarity>
    <Lock>false</Lock>
    <CanGivePassive>false</CanGivePassive>
    <CanReceivePassive>false</CanReceivePassive>
    <InnerType>-1</InnerType>
    <Cost>777</Cost>
    <Script>CindGray_BossManager</Script>
    <Name>The Gray Cinderella / The Ashen Monster</Name>
    <Desc>At the start of each Wave, heal to 50% Max HP if below, and gain The Gray Cinderella passive.

Generate 1 Shin upon hitting a target 5 times, killing a target, or losing 25% of Max HP.

Once per Wave, upon taking lethal damage, negate it and gain damage immunity for the rest of the Scene instead. When this occurs, recover from Stagger and change The Gray Cinderella status to The Ashen Monster at the start of the next Scene.

Upon taking lethal damage, negate it and gain damage immunity for the rest of the Scene. When this occurs, recover from Stagger and heal self for 50% of your Max HP at the start of the next Scene.</Desc>
  </Passive>
</PassiveXmlRoot>